{
    "subject": "resource/La_Lupe",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Cuba",
    "human_readable": "La Lupe originated from Cuba.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.869742751121521,
            "question": "Is La Lupe Cuban?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389960527420044,
            "question": "Where did La Lupe come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.827589750289917,
            "question": "From which nation did La Lupe originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114559054374695,
            "question": "Is Cuba the birthplace of La Lupe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7555842399597168,
            "question": "Can you tell me about La Lupe's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5749606490135193,
            "question": "Where was La Lupe born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715010762214661,
            "question": "In what country was La Lupe raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4912477731704712,
            "question": "What country is La Lupe associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47997865080833435,
            "question": "What is La Lupe's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3397269546985626,
            "question": "What is La Lupe's cultural background?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=La Lupe originated from Cuba.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7800_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is La Lupe's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7800_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is La Lupe associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7800_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was La Lupe raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7800_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7800_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"La Lupe originated from Cuba\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that La Lupe was born in various barrios and cities in Cuba, such as San Pedrito in Santiago de Cuba (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7800/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt), Havana (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7800/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt, 23.txt, and 8.txt), indicating that she has a strong connection to Cuba."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that La Lupe was born in Cuba, which supports the statement \"La Lupe originated from Cuba.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}